[...] @4
Private log: 1/8/2023. Nothing of note to report. @4
All subjects continue to maintain good health and a consistent rate of growth... @5
Same as the last two-hundred and forty days, so whoop-dee-freakin'-doo, @3
break out the fine wine and dance a jig on a lab bench! @4
I'm just... @2
I guess I'm just sick of it. @2 
Sixteen years of top-tier performance, and when the higher-ups finally take notice, @4
they stick me in this musty hole in the middle of nowhere @3
and turn me into a glorified needle-monkey for a bunch of stinkin' rodents. @4
All that double-blind BS about how "critical" and "classified" @4
and "kiss-my-ass-I-don't-care" this is, like some kind of @2
bad spy movie, and their experiment didn't even work? @4
I mean, I assume it didn't. @2
Still not sure what they expected to happen, but @2
whatever this green stuff was supposed to do, clearly it hasn't, so. @4.5
Well, in any case. @1.5
This week I'll administer the last round of doses, @2
then I can finally <color=#99EDC3>dash out</color> of here. @2
Whatever happens or doesn't happen after that is their problem. @4.5
Good. @2.5
Jeez, I'd kill just to take a proper shower right now. @2
[...] @2